Don't say anything, Dave.
Don't say anything.
Okay, you can say something now.
We're still using Zoom, huh?
I can't hear you.
It's all on you, man.
Can you say something?
I'm talking the whole time.
Oh, no, I can't hear you.
Okay, say something.
Yes.
I now hear you.
No.
Yes, yes.
Let me just remind folks.
I don't know if there was a lot of confusion over whether we would meet.
It was speculative.
Where are you, by the way, man?
I'm in Boston.
You're in Boston.
What are you doing in Boston?
Am I ever doing a business trip?
Yeah, I mean, I know that, but like, do you have a team there?
Is it like a
VP meeting?
Bay's here.
Hey.
Are we going to meet Tom?
I hope so.
Who's Borgio Root?
Was that Stefan?
Where's it?
Saved.
Let's meet the icon.
I did not.
I could not, you know, I sort of.
You should have looked at the avatar.
That's what I forget.
Oh, dear God.
We oppose to loot.
Loot.
That's what adventurers call it.
I'm an adventurer.
I don't call it that.
Some of them call it booty.
That just sounds wrong.
This doesn't.
Well, I stayed up late, so I sure hope we get one more person.
Yes.
Let me just slack Stefan.
Yeah, me too.
What are you wearing, Wade?
Bathrobe?
I'm always in my robe when we're playing.
I'm always in my jammies when we get started.
Yeah, he is actually.
Yeah, this is, I'm always in my bathrobe and jamming.
Okay.
It's nine o'clock.
I'm at home.
What do you want?
Some people made poor life choices.
Are you referring to me?
No.
I'm not going out.
You know.
Do you ever go out?
All the time.
I was out at lunch again today with friends.
I actually had lunch, yeah.
But in the evening, not usually.
No, I mean, sometimes, like, it's not too common.
I'm an old man.
You're younger than me.
Well, you're an older man.
Are you single?
Me?
No.
Oh.
No, I'm a fanny bandit.
A what?
I'm a gay.
Well, yeah, I know that, but I didn't know if you were married.
I mean, we're domestically partnered close enough.
You know, I didn't know if you were married or single or between relationships or in a situationship.
It's been quite a few years, right?
It's going to be 20 years this year.
Basically next month.
Oh, well.
Congratulations.
If it were a murder, I'd have been out by now.
There you go.
Does your partner know you use that expression?
Believe me, if somebody could put up with me for 20 years, that would be one of the most tame things they'd have to deal with.
Yeah.
That's what I was about to say.
You were all very impressed with what should we send in the thank you note.
You know, I've never met him all this time.
We've known each other.
Never met him, Wayne.
Never met your wife or any of your kids.
It's true.
It's not that weird, is it?
Well, I'm annoyed that I forced myself to stay awake until midnight and we're not playing.
I agree.
Let's give Stefan two more minutes.
I mean, I remember Gary was like on the fence.
I don't even think he's he committed at all.
I think he's Gary was like, yeah, he was probably not.
Yeah.
That's Stefan.
I mean, he's in France.
What's his excuse?
How do we know him?
He's a cool corporate.
Okay.
And where are you at these days?
Nutanix.
I have an interesting job these days.
I had that moment.
You know that moment when you have a job and it's all going wonderfully until you have that one meeting when you realize it's just like every other fucking company you've ever worked at.
Yeah, for me, that was when What's His Face got up and badmouthed most of the Roku employees.
That was a pretty good day.
I can't remember that it was.
No, we didn't have that.
I did not have that.
Okay, sorry.
You and I have different definitions.
What's his name?
Oh, it was one of the all hands around like 2019 or 2020 or something like that.
It was actually like a whole cavalcade of like Ilya and your boss for a while.
I think.
They said great things like nobody in QA deserves promotions and it's your career own it or get the fuck out, that kind of stuff.
It was, I mean, they didn't say it that crassly, but the undertone was strongly there.
Wow.
Yeah, it was, it was, it's kind of crushing.
Wade is grossly misrepresenting what happened.
So I'm sure that's that's his that's his recollection.
So just to be fair, what matters when you deliver a message as a leader is not what the message is.
It's how it's received.
Oh, yeah.
The snark channels I was in all lit up.
We were all talking shit about that presentation.
I was never invited to the snark channels.
No, you were management.
What?
It's, you know.
Yep.
My one of my employees today, I was DMing him.
I was like, man, you know.
Wait, you've been direct messaging.
David Mendenhallingham, though.
Yes, direct messaging him.
Like, not DMing him.
Like, you're like, you know, our culture is not secrecy, but sometimes the open process just like kills ideas before they even get out of the gate.
Like, we have to give engineers an opportunity to incubate a little bit.
And he's like, oh, yeah, I agree.
We created a Slack channel without you, and we've been talking about this for days.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
The culture that's gotten.
Okay.
Well, if you're not going to include me, I can't help.
Just FYI.
I think, I mean, I think definitely among a lot of rank and file, you know, back while I was still there, there was a lot of frustration.
You know, I was in like two or three different Slack channels with different groups of like a half dozen QA members or hardware team or whatever else.
And they were the all hands were just, they were corporate bingo laughing and stuff like that.
You know, it was people were just kind of tired of it all.
I need to make a mental note.
Well, you and all those people are all gone now.
Oh, yeah.
No, we got the message.
That's that's what that kind of thing is.
It's a filter function put out by management.
And that's what we heard, and we took it.
Okay.
Well, this has been fun, boys.
Hold on, hold on.
We have to go to sleep.
We can do your encounter.
His encounter.
Yeah.
One encounter.
The stolen treasure.
Since you're here, we might as well do the stolen treasure.
All right.
So there's nobody to entertain except Wade.
And Kostas.
And you?
I'd like to think you would be entertained.
He said me.
He said me all right.
Oh, you mean?
I already know what's going to happen here in the driver's seat.
Oh, I'm worried that I don't know what's going to happen.
Right.
So, what is it?
Late at night?
Yes.
Let me just find where people where they should be.
So are you going to be sneaking around like a thief, like a criminal?
I'm a thief?
I'm a criminal?
Sneaking around.
I said sneaking around.
I didn't say.
I will definitely be sneaking around.
That does not make me a thief or a criminal.
Okay.
We'll be sleeping around somehow.
I said, how you might be sneaking around.
I was not.
How might I be sneaking?
Yes.
Kind of like, you know.
Your grandpa, who comes to visit you, and he's a nice guy, and he's a little weird, and you go to bed, and like you go to the bathroom at 2 a.m., and he happens to be awake and going through some drawers.
Okay, like that.
Okay, okay.
So, you know, guest house.
Where's the guest house?
Yeah, where's the guest house?
It's not labeled, is it?
No, no.
Where's the guest?
So, you know, Corwin puts them there.
I see Dora.
She's sleeping in the expensive guest house.
Oh, there's a guest house?
No, yes, but she's sleeping in the expensive one because she didn't.
There is a guest house.
Gatehouse.
It says gatehouse.
Oh, gatehouse, gatehouse.
Big difference between gatehouse.
Yeah, it's like house and gatehouse.
We're in the stable house?
No.
This is the main lodge.
There's like
I just need to find where the damn there is a guest house.
I just don't know where it is.
Ah, there it is.
Okay.
You're in here.
So are you going to wake up and take anybody with you, or are you just going to do this by yourself?
I don't appear to have any real allies in this area.
In this party.
Hold on.
I think, what's his name?
Brewbar likes you, doesn't he?
Brewbar will do anything for you.
He even likes.
Oh, right.
Brewbar.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
What a self-absorbed artist.
The prima donna.
Nobody loves me.
Stefan's not here.
That's why I didn't think of him.
Brewbar is not very sneaky.
No.
Brewbar's approach to things would be to spash.
Although it could, it could be.
You know, he needs his eight hours of rest.
We want him to have all of his rages for tomorrow.
Okay.
All right.
So, yeah, okay.
What's your plan?
It's the middle of the night.
I presume Soma is sleeping in her shell.
Oh, yeah.
Valfyn is bemused, and Brewbar is snoring.
All right.
You walk outside.
It's no, I'm not going outside.
Oh, sorry.
Where am I?
Oh, do not see yourself on the map.
Top left-hand corner.
That's the guest house.
Left guest house?
There is a guest house?
Yes, yes.
Oh, this unlabeled thing by the outhouse.
Okay, over here.
Oh, I see.
Oh, North Yard.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I'm heading for the dining room.
What was in the dining room again?
Now we'll find out.
Okay, I went to the dining room.
You went to the dining room.
Okay.
Crowd in the dining room with the loot.
All right.
You know, so you're in the dining room.
So let's just go through the dining room.
The dining room.
Right.
This is a small second hall flower trophy gallery opens up above an oak dining table surrounded by tall back chairs on the main floor.
Two iron chandeliers hang from the high rafters.
So kind of no occupants, correct?
Yes, no occupants.
I will head upstairs.
So like imagine, I just drew this the square of where the I'm going to upper level of main lodge.
All righty.
Okay, rolling back there.
Well, there, you're up there.
All right.
This is the second, well, this is the second floor.
So you've got the dining room over here.
And I will be walking along here and along here and along here.
Maybe take a look out the window and this window.
And then there's a door.
Okay.
That opens up into what you know to be his bedroom.
That's the idea.
Yep.
All right.
They're going to go into his bedroom here, basically walking into his bedroom.
His bedroom is cozy and warm, but untidy.
Okay.
What would you let me see?
What else is in there?
You mean sorry?
You will see that you do see a closet.
Sorry, not a closet.
Shelf.
That's not a shelf.
What does it call it?
A chest.
You do see a walk-in closet.
He's clearly somebody who's spent a lot of his time, you know, and things look, you know, like a bachelor pad.
So I'm looking for identifying information.
So not, I'm not necessarily looking for treasure or something like that, right?
I'm trying to find something that he kept from the horde that has a name on it, that has some sort of provenance, a unique item that I could describe to someone else, and they'd say, oh, that was that, that was such and such.
Not trying to take anything.
Okay, so you're just looking for something.
I'm looking for information.
Okay.
So you look around and you notice that next to his bedstand, he has a small curio.
Perfect.
And I don't have like mage hand or anything like that, right?
So I've got to go literally up to it.
Yeah, definitely.
Yes.
Yes, you do.
Okay.
I do have silence as a ritual spell.
Okay, I could let you.
So maybe I should cast that on the room.
Yes, that would be a good thing.
I would say that is a good idea.
I always forget that silence is like that in D and D.
What?
That it, you know, it's a literal.
I'm used to the Final Fantasy silence where it's just no spells.
Oh, yeah.
I forget that silence is actually more useful.
All right.
You managed to cast silence.
It's.
Okay.
So I'm going to just.
So it's a 20-foot radius or a 20-foot sphere?
20-foot radius sphere.
20-foot sphere.
All right.
Let's just drop.
Radius or no, 10-foot radius.
That would be.
20-foot radius.
It's linked in the.
All right.
Yeah.
The place is there.
So that's definitely going to cover the room.
I'm assuming you're covering both rooms, so Sir Dar can't hear you as well.
Sure, might as well, right?
Yes.
I'm just kind of like even better.
Look at that.
Even the hallway is quiet.
All right.
So you I guess you walk up and pick up the curio
and inspect it.
And inspect it.
Let's see.
Okay.
It is a
okay.
It's a pair of wooden elven ears attached by a golden by a copper chain, by a golden chain.
Okay.
Wow.
That's weird.
It's going to be a tough one to place.
Can I run that through Google Lens?
You also find a delicate wooden square carved with a labyrinth maze.
Do I recognize the labyrinth in any way?
Is it a famous labyrinth?
No, there's not.
No, no history checks I can make or anything like that.
Arcana.
You could.
And then I'd have to.
I'd have to.
Do you have to make something up if I roll wild?
Let's see.
I guess.
Roll 20, roll 20.
19.
Close enough.
Pretty good.
Better than I expected.
So indeed, you do find something.
You do recognize this labyrinth maze as from legend, from stories you've heard about the Undercity of Waterdeep.
Okay.
From Waterdeep?
Yes.
So Elven and Wooden Elven Ears maybe from Waterdeep.
Perhaps.
Well, these are two different things.
These are two different things.
Okay.
Right.
And then you notice a drawer underneath.
That's tempting.
Do you want to open the drawer?
Definitely.
Now, unfortunately, it's locked.
Ah, well.
You have thieves' tools.
No.
Not a thief.
I'm a bard.
Okay.
So you're going to have to break it.
You're not going to be able to pick it.
Awesome.
Hang on a second.
Just see if I have any other ideas.
Well, you can't cast any spells with a verbal component, that's for sure.
You can drop the silence.
Nope.
I need that.
Yeah.
Keeping me alive.
I mean, if no sound could be created, I guess you don't want to smash it.
I don't even know what I would smash it with.
I'd have to like force it with a dagger.
Yes.
Yeah.
If you roll high enough, what skill is that?
Sleight of Hand.
Oh, it's Sleight of Hand.
Yes.
But don't forget you have that plus 10.
I got a 10.
Are you using your plus 10 to augment it?
You have a bardic inspiration.
Oh, yeah.
But like you can augment it by.
I got to remember how that.
Only if I fail a D20 test, then I can add.
Hey, sure, why not?
Might as well go for it.
All right.
So 13.
You successfully managed to pry open the drawer.
The drawer.
It wasn't.
The Falcon never thought anyone would actually go into his room and actually steal something.
I didn't steal anything.
Yeah, he's just exploring.
He's saying it's like DC12 or something like that.
Yeah, okay.
It's like, he's just sort of, you know, so you look inside, and there you find a small iron box in the shape of a dragon's head.
It has a small, a small, you know, key where you can.
Wind up key.
Yeah, wind-up key doesn't care.
Whatever.
You mean it's like a toy?
Like you wind it up and it makes dragon sounds or something?
It's underneath the box.
You don't know.
You'd have to turn it.
He won't hear it.
Well, I guess we're silenced.
Sure, why not?
Let's play the game.
All right.
You rotate the key and then the dragon's head.
The dragon's head opens its jaw, right?
And out of its jaw, a brass ring with the lightning word lightning carved in Elvish and Sylvan script.
Okay.
So we've got a ring, we've got wooden elveniers, we've got a labyrinth under Waterdeep.
Yes.
Right.
A lot of carry stuff.
We'll definitely be able to solve this mystery.
Right.
So those are, so those are the four sort of like interesting items you found.
All right.
I think that's good.
Let's try to put everything back.
Of course, he's going to notice that his lock's been smashed, but nothing's been taken.
In fact, you leave something behind.
You could leave a little money behind for the note saying for the damages.
No, that's all right.
I don't really like him.
You don't really like him?
No, but I'm going to pretend to like him because I want everyone to be friends with me.
Right.
Rollessitus, but not a thief.
Roll a history check.
History.
Another history check.
Yes.
And I guess another bardic inspiration.
To wash.
Well, I don't think bardic inspiration is going to complement that one.
Well, there was a whole bunch of lore you were about to discover about the ring, but you don't.
Okay.
You, dude.
I'm just joking.
Other people can inspect the ring.
Are you leaving the ring?
You're saying if I were to take it with me?
I'm not going to take it.
I'm not going to do that.
That would be what the common thief would do.
All right.
Do you want to take any notes about the ring?
Any details?
Oh, yeah.
Lots of notes.
You know, when I get back to the guest house, I pull out my quill and my paper and I write a poem about the wonders of the dragon horde.
All right.
And pictures and sketches and everything I can remember.
And one more detail.
Do you roll a, I guess, this is like some performance checks.
No, not, I should not move.
I should need to move you, not him.
Performance.
Yes, performance.
I don't know.
What would be sleight of hands, stealth?
Something for how well you do your drawing.
Oh.
Because it was kind of probably performance.
Yeah.
Something artistic.
I'm going to.
I'm going to add some bardic inspiration to that one.
11.
All right.
So you have enough of something that people would recognize.
And with the disadvantage, they could get some significant lore.
Okay.
But you did not get a precise, you know, perfect picture of it.
Do you draw the other ones as well, I presume?
Sure.
For all of them, I presume.
Yeah, as much detail as I can remember.
Okay.
You do remember one additional detail.
As you were kind of inspecting it and trying to, you know, put it into memory and draw the artistic thing.
You do notice that on the chain that holds the ears, there's sort of a my dearly beloved kind of that kind of makes you wonder what exactly is going on here.
And he has a suitor.
And then the dragon head looks remarkably realistic.
Okay.
Like it's not just, you know, some like.
Like it might actually be the dragon in miniature form.
Yes, it's sort of like very oddly realistic.
More so than such a toy mechanism you've seen in the past.
Perhaps some magic was put to use or who knows what.
19 Arcana.
On what?
On the miniaturized dragon.
The miniaturized dragon.
Well, as you inspect, so as you inspect the miniaturized dragon, you realize that it isn't the dragon itself.
But if it isn't, it is a remarkably anatomically correct version of its head.
It's almost as if someone cut off its head, shrunk it down to size.
Okay.
And keeps it inside of his closet as some kind of reminder or a memento.
Roll a history check.
Another check.
13.
So, the best you've been able to figure out from these investigations is that Falcon the Hunters had some kind of relationship to the person who had the ears.
Now, you don't understand why somebody would keep ears around, but you know, lots of different cultures.
Who are you to judge?
Blah, blah, blah.
Right?
The dragon head was interesting, but what you do, but what you're speculating, what you think is that that ring must be from the dragon horde.
Yeah, that seems to make sense.
But the falcon, the best guess is whoever these ears belong to was hurt by the dragon, and the way for him to torment the dragon is to shove a piece of his horde in its mouth forever.
Oh, that's an interesting theory.
Your treasure kind of thing.
Right.
In other words, that he sort of took the head, miniaturized it, and shoved a coin as sort of a way to shove it to the dragon.
So, this was just a gold ring with elvish writing on it.
Lightning.
Yeah, the word lightning, I would surname
Valfine would have translated it for you.
You do make an interesting connection to all of the to the last that remember how you met those two orcs, shaman orcs, who were related to the god of Talos and lightning.
We also, when we went to the lighthouse, the lighthouse was dedicated to the god Talos.
Right.
That was the other shaman.
You've met two shamans right now, half-orc shamans.
Okay.
Hold on.
I forgot to tell you what color the dragon is.
Oh.
This is a blue dragon.
Hmm.
More lightning.
Also, Orsic killed a blue dragon.
Yes.
Said to forced an blue dragon to go make an infernal pact.
So there's your there.
There's so what you're doing.
Okay.
I hope this will all be written in the summary because I'm not going to remember all the time.
Yeah, and I'm very happy that I'm recording all of this because yeah, you're going to have to write it all down.
But a lot.
So what you did was you discovered a miniaturized dragon head with a ring that had in Elvish the word lightning.
Probably some weird memento, you're thinking.
Probably some vengeful vindictiveness by shoving the ring inside the mouth.
And at the same time, you do know that there seems to be a resurgence of the evil god Talos and the shamans in the area.
And you do recall that he wanted you to get rid of some half-orcs in the woodland manse.
The hunter did.
Yes.
Yeah, he wanted us to go on that orc quest.
Right.
And, you know, you're beginning to sense that he might have a thing against people who, you know, deal with lightning.
He's opposed to the god Talos.
Or it might be much more personal than that.
Well, I think this was a pretty successful reconnaissance mission.
Yeah.
Got lucky with some roles.
Really, only one bad role.
Right.
I mean, yeah, could have gone much worse.
The spell worked.
Yes.
In the morning, the Falcon Hunter discovers his broken broken thing.
Drawer, drawer, whatever.
Looks inside of it, is frantically, notices that everything is, oh, roll your performance.
You roll your stealth to see whether how close you got everything back to where it was.
One more roll, huh?
Yes.
Oh, boy.
Eight.
Well, he definitely notices that things were moved around, which confuses him even more.
Who does this?
Right.
So he marches.
He looks in the drawer and doesn't take the treasure.
Yeah.
Who doesn't do such a thing?
Wait a minute.
I've got that non-treasure havoc guy in our midst.
Maybe he should roll his perception if he figures out the puzzle.
Oh, no.
No, no, he has comes to a very different conclusion.
When you arrive all for breakfast in the morning, the falcon says, looks at the four of you and says, the cult of Talos came into my house to steal the artifact, yet they did not steal it.
Artifact?
He pulls out the ring and he says, this is from Imrith's horde.
Imrith.
Yes.
Welcome back.
Imrith's horde.
The clerics of Talos view the doom of the desert as one of the favorite of Talos and want any piece of that gold, that treasure hoard for themselves as a sacrifice, an offering to Talos.
But the fools did not know how to manipulate the machinery that would cause the dragonhead to spit it out.
Oh, okay.
He thinks that I have not seen the ring.
I got it.
Right.
So he's like, this ring belonged to Imrith's horde.
Wow.
Can we see it?
He goes, yes, but I want it back.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Of course.
You know, I've never seen an artifact from a dragon horde before.
He 24 deception.
I think you fooled him.
You absolutely, I mean, and that is with your silver tongue effect?
It's a natural.
I didn't need it.
I think I rolled a 19.
No, no, no.
That's a natural 20.
It's green.
Oh, no, I got a natural 20.
Yeah.
So you just like nailed it, right?
Okay.
So he's, you've completely nailed it.
He's believing anything you want to tell him.
So tell him what you want.
So you've never seen a dragon horde.
Is that where you're going?
Okay.
You are able to pick up the ring and hand it to me.
We should pass it around.
Yeah, I want to improve my picture, right?
Remember, my picture wasn't very good.
Yes.
So I will assume that now you can improve it.
You're in daylight, you notice the imperfections, and you create a faithful reproduction.
Falcon, the Falcon Hunter, picks up the ring and says, Imrith, and he pauses.
He says, Imrith was my party.
When I was an adventurer, we faced Imrith.
I was the only one to escape.
And when I heard she was dead, I had to go and see for myself.
And I made it to her hoard where her body wasn't found, and most of her hoard had been plundered.
And dragon bodies and corpses were all littered across the floors and fields.
But I did find this ring among all of all of the treasure.
I thought that he used his share of the dragon horde to build this whole well.
You can ask him now.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
He goes, was that the dragon horde you used to build this lodge?
He leans over.
I got a reputation to maintain.
I guess I'm just not following.
He got the money from somewhere.
Yes, he goes, I did.
Well, okay, so what happened was I showed up at Imrith's horde.
Everybody had gone.
Everybody had debt.
Everybody had stolen.
But there was enough, you know, bits and pieces of gold for me to get enough money to build this.
Well, there was still enough.
Dragon hordes are huge, right?
It'd probably take days to clear it all out.
And he goes, it wasn't, and it wasn't that they were, it's like, I don't need that much money to build a place like this.
I just needed, you know, a bunch of money to buy some land out in the middle of nowhere.
It was really just seed capital, that's all we're looking for here, right?
He goes, this is not the D round.
This is, you know, angel investment.
This is angel investment territory.
No, this is friends and family.
This is your mom.
This is your friend.
This is friends.
This is pre-angel.
It's friends and family.
That's right.
He's like, look, I've been working at this place for 20 years.
I mean, I've built this place up.
Yeah, I found a little bit of cash there.
But you can't tell anybody that I didn't actually face a dragon.
Oh, your secret's safe with me.
I got to butter him up a little bit.
You know, after what happened yesterday, I got to get him back on my side.
Need more friends.
All right, do a persuasion.
Sure.
Why not?
I just want to see if you get the 20.
23.
All right.
You don't quite get the natural.
I'm not a natural 20.
You know, he's starting to see that you're not a bad guy.
I just had a bad day yesterday.
Yeah, he realizes that you had a bad day.
You know, he actually appreciates your integrity and your honesty now and your willingness and your willingness to stand on your principles.
Still doesn't agree with them, but it says, you know, and he goes, look, I didn't, it was there.
There was, there was, I, I was a bit of a scavenger.
I was looking for something for no closure.
And I found the ring and I found a few scattered coins that nobody would go missing.
All right.
And I, and I used that to buy this land.
So, yes, I'm, I'm a bit of a fake.
Now, you have to understand, it's good for business for people to think that I faced a dragon and defeated it and stole its horde, right?
It kind of goes with the whole business.
It goes like Falcon the Hunter, who stole what was left over from the dragon horde, does not sound as imposing as Falcon the Hunter, killer of dragons.
It's a lot more honest, though.
I agree.
Yeah.
You know, Simmon, you're absolutely right, but I'm trying to run a business here.
This is that there's a people come here because they want to
see the location and the food is good.
And the fantasy of dining with a dragon slayer.
Right.
Yes, exactly.
And then they feel sick.
That's why we came here.
We came here because there was promise of good wine, right?
Like for a brewberry?
Yes.
That was a reason, yeah.
Yeah.
I'm just saying.
There's other reasons people come here.
Sure.
It's like Disneyland.
You can go there for lots of different reasons.
Yeah, for lots.
Some people like the rides, some people like the characters.
Yes.
Some people who hate having money on Main Street.
He explains that the kind of clientele that he likes that attracts, there's a kind of clientele that wants to hang out with the Falcon the Hunter and hear about his hunts and the dragon horde and the dragon that he faced.
Interesting.
He might have a silver tongue of his own.
Is he part barred?
No, he's just trying to explain that there's a, you know, it's not, it's not, I don't, he goes, I don't, I don't have your silvery tongue, Vucradin.
But, you know, when people are here, they want to believe.
Makes it easier.
Right.
They, they, that, when they've paid money to come see me and they've heard my story, they don't want to be know that the story's fake.
They want to believe the story.
Yeah.
The Winchester Mystery House.
He goes, Can we, can we, can we keep that story between ourselves, Vukradin and Brewberry?
I don't have any problem with that.
And Valfine and Sony.
I have no reason to rat him out.
Okay.
I don't particularly agree with it, but it's not my place to intervene there.
All right.
Okay.
So Valfine would see it as a totally normal thing to do.
Valfine is very impressed.
Yeah.
She's like perfectly, perfectly normal.
This is like, she's actually feeling a little bit disappointed that she didn't think of this as a genius.
No, more of like, why she didn't pick up on this immediately.
Like, of course, this would be the case.
A single ranger who has a dragon horde, that makes no sense.
All right.
Sounds like that was a successful outing.
We all got long rested and we can move on with our lives to the next destination.
We got to deliver the goods, right?
Yes.
Yeah.
All right.
So we can save that for next week.
Yeah.
So I'm probably going to meet in two weeks next week.
I'll send a note.
I'll send a note if next week's going to happen, but I'm going to be in India.
So I have no election day.
Which one?
November 4th.
It's election day.
The U.S.
Yeah.
Did you ballot?
You didn't vote?
I mean, it's local election, not federal.
Oh, I voted for my, I voted.
I just, because I did via mailing, I don't actually know the date.
That's all.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I made sure to submit my paperwork.
You don't get
and right.
See you then.
All right, guys.
I'll send a note next week about us possibly meeting.
You're going to be in India, right?
I'm not going.
I had to cancel.
Well, why's that?
I don't want to get into it.
All right.
Sorry.
None of our business.
Got it.
Bye-bye.
All right.
Hey.
Okay.
Well, I'm glad we stuck around and had a little bit of fun.
Take care.
That's good.
Thanks.
All right.
Take care.
Bye-bye.
Good night.